So the first step in building Aosp is to execute the EMV setup dot as such.
So this command is executed using the Linux source command.
So to execute the N.V. setup, we use this command source build slash EMV setup.
So basically we are trying to execute the EMV setup DOT as a shell script which resides within build
folder.
And the source command is basically a built in shell command that reads and executes the file candidate
in the current shell.
So in this case, the source command will read the EMV setup dot search line by line and it will get
executed.
So you can also replace source with simply a dot.
The dot works as a kind of alias to the source command, so let's do this.
So once this command is executed, we get access to a lot of other commands.
The full list of available commands can be seen by running X.
Mm hmm.
Displays all the commands which are available for us.
Now, let's look at the most common commands from this list.
So as the first step, it is necessary to load the lunch script.
The lunch command, this command.
The lunch command shows you the lunch menu.
Yes.
You can compare this to the lunch menu, which is served in a restaurant.
So this lunch command serves you with the build variants available for Aosp.
So you can just simply type lunch and now it will show you the lunch menu.
So here is our lunch menu.
We have 73 flavors, so each of the builder up are for different purpose.
So as you can see, each of the build flavor has different keywords.
So here you can see these four arm architecture CPUs and there is EMG stands for Engineering Build and
here arm 64 bit.
Similarly you can see x 86 the Intel and AMD processors 36 and you can see borne out all of these are
for different types of devices.
And here we could see high key.
High key is the development board which we normally use, which we commonly use for Aosp similarly big
board.
So there are different boards build flavors and the one with C of these are for the cuttlefish.